[Music]
you know they call me Smash and dash I'm
posting that everyone because you're my
friend you
because
hey you look a lot different in your
profile picture let me see
close enough all right cool all right
you got some nice wood in
it hi handsome how can I help you um we
wanted to cash this check actually
please with pleasure meaning it will be
very pleasurable for
me dorm enim attainment are you guys
starving students are you stripping to
pay tuition because you look like a
stripper no not you you look like a
Mighty Duck actually is dorm tment it's
not that hard as you were saying um yeah
we do sketch comedy and stuff I love
comedy make me laugh okay like we really
don't do that type
of oh my God that's so hilarious now I
just wish you'd make my vagina
laugh hey guys how you guys doing who
wants to get robbed huh okay listen
here's what's going to happen you
you're going to do what I
say or I'm going to blow kid and play's
brains out okay I'm just going to show
Rome something upstairs but my roommate
Carrie is dying to meet you yo Carrie
the guys on the internet videos
here
no
hey I'm Carrie I don't care you're a lot
cuter in person I'm cute and un
person
too do you want anything and I
mean
anything listen I don't know who told
you what or what you know but I have a
girlfriend okay so you can't do nothing
for me and I mean
nothing do you want a drink yeah I'll
take something to drink I'm kind of
thirsty so uh what do you want to drink
we have fi perier Gatorade you got
anything that ain't French Gatorade I'll
take Gatorade I'll take Gatorade you
know my daddy used to work for
Gatorade mhm he be having all the new
flavors and Thunder blast tornado
wind ocean salt yeah interesting mhm you
know I don't really like telling people
that though cuz then they only going to
want me for my gator con that you know
cuz you need a girl who going to want
you gator where's the Starbucks
T Chad come on man let's walk man you
got it let's keep walking man cuz Fu you
know what excuse me sir you know where I
can sh at can you know Chaz we not doing
that man we have respect don't don't do
that chat come on oh
oh the Grim is coming out my
ass oh God give me the money you
just don't hurt him oh don't hurt
this one you like this one give me the
money you put it through
the slit now not with the
shaming take the money you know what
they say once you go black we
don't want you back all right what else
you guys I ain't got what's this sh huh
a check do I look like I got a license
huh stupid piece of give me your
watch man my daddy gave me this watch
your daddy could suck this
just like you're going to suck both of
these
I'm out you guys kid in play
could suck a
dick do you think I'm a I
am that was
fun uh-uh uh-uh you are not trying to
leave
already listen
uh ch ch no no I know I got it I got it
uh i' I've been thinking and this this
isn't going to work out between me and
you just go that's cool get out I don't
know you like Gatorade what the hell
get off of my friend he has a
girlfriend but I don't you just had sex
with my roommate we just broke up you
know what I'm
saying I'm hungry again man do you ever
stop eating NS no basically I got like a
Greek god of body so Zeus came down like
there you go know what I'm saying ain't
that where the car used to be
at like I'm tripping right where's the
car where's the where's the car where's
the car where's the car I thought y' was
at the car y'all supposed to stay by the
car yeah okay you said that but someone
stole the car why you carrying Mone he
was sexually assaulted by
one freeze Black Street make a move I'll
shoot you right in your fuboo jeans have
you guys been robbing check cash in
places huh no sir no sir you throw a gun
in a little white girl's face you got
her all scared and
horny that little pervert was freaking
out you guys listen to some little John
get all crunked up all fired up start
riding dirty drinking that Codine
officer we had nothing to do with that
why did I get a report that you did that
it was dick sucking robber or he was
talking a lot about sucking dick I don't
know what's up with the little guy huh
what are you smiling at little guy Turn
Down for What I just help my friend
he just H he hold my butt cheeks open
while I was whoop there it
isn't that's your problem C you always
playing stop playing if they didn't
leave a car this would have never
happened they the ones that left the car
shut the up man hey Pang Clan knock
it off hey who the you calling Pang
[Music]
clam